

BIRTHDAY DATE 30 MAY 1995 (28)

Portfolio netiphoc.github.io

Contact

Phone

094-532-3576

Email

neti.phoc@gmail.com

Skills

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE:

- C# (Proficient)
- VB.NET (Intermediate)
- Java (Basic)

SOFTWARE/TOOL:

- Unity 3D (Proficient)
- Unity Mirror/Steam networking and multiplayer (Intermediate)
- Maya (Intermediate)
- FMOD Sound Engine (Intermediate)

Language

English (Intermediate)

Thai (Native)

NETI PHOCHOT (Jay)

GAME PROGRAMMER

Passionate about game programming using C# and Unity3D Engine. Interested in software development. With 5 years experience in C# programming. I want to be a part of programmer in gaming industry to create a collection of games that can connect all people together and bring people joy.

Education

2019 - 2023

BANGKOK UNIVERSITY

School of Information Technology and Innovation

Major in Games and Interactive Media (GPA: 3.71)

Experience

Q 2019 - 2023

Clone Hero X

Mobile game project

- A classic instrument based rhythm game for Android
- 10K total download on PlayStore

Wanonn Party

Steam game project

- Online game, a party game for 40 players.

Listen me

Thesis, Steam game project

- Online game, a puzzle game for 4 players.

2023 - Present

Moo-Kata Cafe Simulator

Individual game Project

- Offline game, a Moo-Kata cafe business simulation game
- Large scale project made by only me within 7 months for **portfolio**

Trashappbin website (Founders)

Lightweight program site

- A collection of lightweight program made with Unity3D Engine